educationab.com 2016-02-27

# Privacy Policy « Education Information and Education News

### [Privacy Policy ](http://www.educationab.com/privacy-policy/)

Education2012.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. At Distance-Education.org, we value and respect your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and usage practices for this web site: http://www.Education2012.com. It covers:

What personally identifiable information is collected from you through our website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared;  
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data;  
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information;  
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collected Education2012.com is the sole owner of the information collected on our website. We do collect personal information about you when you submit information or register on this website. “Personal Information” means information that would allow a party to contact you, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number, or email address. On this website, we collect your full name and email in order so that we may contact you or so that you can participate in sections that require registration or user input. 

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Cookies**

This site uses cookies. Cookies are only used for registration purposes only. We do not have control or rights over the actions of these cookies. At some places on the Distance-Education.org web site, the use of a cookie may be offered in the future in order to allow Distance-Education.org to measure activity on the site and to make improvements and updates based on which areas are popular and which are not. Cookies may also be used to improve your user experience. 

Some of our advertising partners use cookies when you visit their website from this site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Use of Personal Information Education2012.com does not share any personally identifying information with third parties.

**Log Files/Web Traffic Reporting**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We use web analytic tracking and reporting services to solely track the search engines on our server and keep these reports for internal use. Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do not use these reports to identify individual users except in cases of deliberate misuse of our systems. We do not share our server usage logs with third parties.  

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via e-mail or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Registration**

In some areas of this site, you will be asked to provide information that will used to follow-up with you. Your participation is completely optional. If you do decide to register on this website and provide your contact information, you agree to allow Distance-Education.org to contact you via email.

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please use the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter email you recieved to opt-out of communication from us. You can also contact us.

**Notification of Change** s

If we decide to change our terms of use, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

### Online Courses 

Description Initially, you’ll diagnose your strengths and weaknesses in reading ability through a questionnaire that will show your reading habits...

Cisco CCNA Internetworking Technologies 2 Course Code: DED3500-B School: Distance-Education.org Enroll NowCourse Materials Available: 90 Days Estimated...

Welcome to our Expert Certificate Medical Terminology course Learning medical terminology is like learning any foreign language. Along with the vocabulary,...

Description Master the art of selling! Our comprehensive range of sales and consulting training modules are built into a complete library that equips you...

Description Many body masseurs are now applying their skills and techniques into the sporting arena with great success. This type of treatment is finding...

Advanced Technical Writing Course Code: DED235-A School: Distance-Education.org Enroll NowCourse Materials Available: 6 Weeks Estimated Hours to Complete...
